thelittleappfactory.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy – The Little App Factory

## Privacy Policy

#### What personal information about customers does thelittleappfactory.com gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at thelittleappfactory.com. Here are the types of information we gather:

  * Information you give us: we receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
  * Automatic information: we receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies”, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses thelittleappfactory.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of thelittleappfactory.com on other Web sites. 
  * E-mail communications: we compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please unsubscribe from our mailing list.
  * Information from other sources: we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

#### Does thelittleappfactory.com share the information it receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries The Little App Factory, Pty., Ltd., controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.

  * Affiliated businesses we do not control: we work closely with affiliated businesses. In some cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party.
  * Third-party service providers: we employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * Promotional offers: sometimes we send offers to selected groups of thelittleappfactory.com customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your subscription preference.
  * Business transfers: as we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that The Little App Factory, PTY, LTD, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * Protection of thelittleappfactory.com and others: we release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of thelittleappfactory.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
  * With your consent: other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

#### How secure is information about me?

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

#### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit thelittleappfactory.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New South Whales, Australia. If you have any concern about privacy at thelittleappfactory.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
